Preliminary Guide to the DoubleTake Records, 1908-1999 (bulk 1993-1999)
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession (2010-0081): DoubleTake Records, 1993-1998, (41 boxes) (Box 3)
  - Kleitsch, Chad (Box 18)
  - Klett, Mark (Box 18)
  - Klich, Kent (Box 18)
  - Klipper, Stuart (Box 18)
  - Klugman, Karen (Box 18)
  - Koch, Ferne (Box 18)
  - Koga, Mary (Box 18)
  - Konic, Stephanie (Box 18)
  - Kosarich, Rick (Box 18)
  - Koster, Axel (Box 18)
  - Kotchen, Robert (Box 18)
  - Kral, Jan (Box 18)
  - Kranz, Nancy (Box 18)
  - Kratochvil, Antonin (2 folders) (Box 18)
  - Kuhn, Penny (Box 18)
  - Kunhardt, Amelia (Amy) (Box 18)
  - Kuo, Alex (Box 18)
  - Kurspahic, Kemal (Box 18)
  - Kwiatkowska, Michelle (Box 18)
  - Ladd, Jeff (Box 18)
  - Landy, Neal (Box 18)
  - Lane, Joni (Box 18)
  - Lang, Mary Stuart (Box 18)
  - Lang, Michael (Box 18)
  - Lange, Dorothea (Box 18)
  - Langer, Jason (Box 18)
  - Lantos, Lauren (Box 18)
  - Larsen, Flynn (Box 18)
  - Larson, Krisitine (Box 18)
  - Lassalle, Sebastian (Box 18)
  - Laughlin, Ray (Box 18)
  - Lavigne, Jill (Box 18)
  - Lawrence, John (Box 18)
  - Layton, Elizabeth (Box 18)
  - Le, An-My (Box 18)
  - Le, Thinh (Box 18)
  - Leaken, Kitty (Box 18)
  - Ledford, Stretch (Box 18)
  - Ledger, Bill (Box 18)
  - Ledochowski, Chris (Box 18)
  - Lee, Bud (Box 18)
  - Lee, Jocelyn (Box 18)
  - Lee, Lance (Box 19)
  - Lee, Chang (Box 19)
  - Lee, Susan (Box 19)
  - Lee, Ron (Box 19)
  - Leebrick, Gil (Box 19)
  - Lehman, Steve (Box 19)
  - Lehr, John (Box 19)
  - Leiter, Saul (Box 19)
  - Lekberg, Andrea (Box 19)
  - Lemonick, Eileen Hohmuth (Box 19)
  - Leonard, Joanne (Box 19)
  - Leong, Mark (Box 19)
  - Lepkoff, Rebecca (Box 19)
  - Lerager, James (Box 19)
  - Leskovak, Diana (Box 19)
  - Lester, Alvin (Box 19)
  - Lesy, M./Detroit Publishing Co. (Box 19)
  - Lewis, Payne (Box 19)
  - Levitt - Mexico (8 folders) (Box 19)
  - Letinsky, Laura (Box 20)
  - Letourneau, John (Box 20)
  - Levenstein, Matvey (Box 20)
  - Levin, Meryl (2 folders) (Box 20)
  - Levin, Mimi (Box 20)
  - Levin, Wayne (2 folders) (Box 20)
  - Levine, Anna (Box 20)
  - Levine, Ron (Box 20)
  - Levins, Mike (Box 20)
  - Levinthal, David (Box 20)
  - Levthold, Catherine (Box 20)
  - Levy, Alyson (Box 20)
  - Levy, Builder (Box 20)
  - Levy, Janice (Box 20)
  - Levy, Rob (Box 20)
  - Lewis, Michael (Box 20)
  - Lichtenstein, Alex (Box 20)
  - Liebling, Jerome (Box 20)
  - Liftin, Joan (Box 20)
  - Light, Ken (Box 20)
  - Lindman, Peter (Box 20)
  - Linnemeier-Marshall, Lynn (Box 20)
  - Lipper, Susan (Box 20)
  - Lippman, Susan (Box 20)
  - Llerena, Roberto (Box 20)
  - Locke, Kris (Box 20)
  - Loewenberg, Ina (Box 20)
  - Loengard, John (Box 20)
  - Lomax, Alan (Box 20)
  - Lorusso, Nicola (Box 20)
  - Lowe, Jeffrey (Box 20)
  - Lozowick, Louis (Box 21)
  - Luckett, James (Box 21)
  - Lueders-Booth, John (Box 21)
  - Luster, Debbie (Box 21)
  - Lutter, Vera (Box 21)
  - Lutzen, Andre (Box 21)
  - Lynch, David (Box 21)
  - Lynnworth, Jill (Box 21)
  - Lynton, Holly (Box 21)
  - Lyon, Danny (3 folders) (Box 21)
  - Lyons, Robert (Box 21)
  - MacDougall, Mal (Box 21)
  - MacNeil, Wendy Snyder (Box 21)
  - MacWeeney, Alan (Box 21)
  - Maher, Mike (Box 21)
  - Maisel, David (Box 21)
  - Manheimer, Kara (Box 21)
  - Manly, Roger (Box 21)
  - Mann, Robert (Box 21)
  - Mann, Sally (Box 21)
  - Marasco, Rose (Box 21)
  - Marden, Malerie (Box 21)
  - Marin, Richard (Box 21)
  - Marin, Roger (Box 21)
  - Mariner's Museum (Box 22)
  - Marino, Carol (Box 22)
  - Mark, Mary Ellen (Box 22)
  - Maroukian, Francine (Box 22)
  - Marshall, Karen (Box 22)
  - Marshall, Kerry (Box 22)
  - Martin, Carl (Box 22)
  - Mason, Charles (Box 22)
  - Maul, Tim (Box 22)
  - Menszer (Box 22)
  - Martin, Daria (Box 22)
  - Maslov (Box 22)
  - Matheson, Elizabeth (Box 22)
  - Mattison, Harry (Box 22)
  - Mauskopf, Norman (Box 22)
  - Mays, Elaine (Box 22)
  - McAdams, Dona Ann (Box 22)
  - McClintock, Lesley (Box 22)
  - McCormack, Forrest (Box 22)
  - McCormick, Chandra (Box 22)
  - McCourt, Everett (Box 22)
  - McDonald, Anne Arden (Box 22)
  - McDonough, Paul (Box 22)
  - McDowell, Bill (Box 22)
  - McElroy, Michael (Box 22)
  - McGowen (Box 22)
  - McGregor, Merideth (Box 22)
  - McGovern, Tom (Box 23)
  - McGuirk, Paul (Box 23)
  - McKenna, Rollie (Box 23)
  - McKibben, Bill (Box 23)
  - McLain, David (Box 23)
  - McLean, Patricia (Box 23)
  - McMahon, Conette (Box 23)
  - McNair, Giles (Box 23)
  - McPherson, Larry (Box 23)
  - McPhillips, Ramsey (Box 23)
  - McWilliams, John (Box 23)
  - Meiselas, Susan (Box 23)
  - Mendoza, Tony (Box 23)
  - Mermelstein, Jeff (Box 23)
  - Merritt, Sandra (Box 23)
  - Messina, Elizabeth (Box 23)
  - Meyer, Kurt (with Pam Deuel) (Box 23)
  - Meyer, Pedro (Box 23)
  - Meyerowitz, Joel (2 folders) (Box 23)
  - Meyer, Jeffrey (Box 23)
  - Michahelles, Sandro (Box 23)
  - Michaels, Duane (Box 23)
  - Mieth, Hansel (Box 23)
  - Milanowski, Stephen R. (Box 23)
  - Milisenda, John (Box 23)
  - Miller, Brian (Box 23)
  - Miller, Howard Seth (Box 24)
  - Miller, John (Box 24)
  - Miller, Ken (Box 24)
  - Miller, Peter, APX, Inc. (Box 24)
  - Miller, Rex (Box 24)
  - Miller, Sybil (Box 24)
  - Miller, Van (Box 24)
  - Miller, Wayne F. (Box 24)
  - Milnor, Daniel (2 folders) (Box 24)
  - Mintz, Brad (Box 24)
  - Mircik, Laura (Box 24)
  - Mirer, Daniel (Box 24)
  - Misrach, Richard (2 folders) (Box 24)
  - Mississippi Self-Portrait (Box 24)
  - Missbach, Leah (Box 24)
  - Mitchel, Julio (Box 24)
  - Miuccio, Liana (Box 24)
  - Miyoshi, Kozo (Box 24)
  - Modica, Andrea (Box 24)
  - Mofokeng, Santu (Box 24)
  - Molenhuis, Jacob (Box 24)
  - Monastario, Pablo (Box 24)
  - Monfort, Regina (Box 24)
  - Montag, Daro (Box 24)
  - Monroe, Gary (2 folders) (Box 24)
  - Montgomery, Scott (Box 25)
  - Monroe, Peter (Box 25)
  - Moody, Phil (Box 25)
  - Moos, Viviane (Box 25)
  - Moran, Nancy (Box 25)
  - Morrell, Abe (Box 25)
  - Morgenstern, Eve (Box 25)
  - Moriarty, Brian (Box 25)
  - Morphew, Lisa (Box 25)
  - Morris, Chris (Box 25)
  - Morris, David Rae (Box 25)
  - Morton, Margaret (Box 25)
  - Moser, Lida (Box 25)
  - Moses, John (Box 25)
  - Mosier, Phillip (Box 25)
  - Mott, Michele (Box 25)
  - Mueller, Laura (Box 25)
  - Muhammad, Nzingah (Box 25)
  - Mullaney, Peter (Box 25)
  - Mullins, Pictureman (Box 25)
  - Murray, Felicia (Box 25)
  - Murray, Katie (Box 25)
  - Myers, Art (Box 25)
  - Myers, Joan (Box 25)
  - Nabokov, Dominique (Box 25)
  - Nance, Marilyn (Box 25)
  - NASA (Box 25)
  - Neel, David (Box 25)
  - Neff, Thomas (Box 25)
  - Nelson, Erik (Box 25)
  - Neto, Mario Cravo (Box 25)
  - Neumann, William (Box 25)
  - Nevel, Jocelyn (Box 25)
  - Newton, Robert (Box 25)
  - Nicol, James (Box 25)
  - Nicoll, Link (Box 25)
  - Nicosia, Nic (Box 25)
  - Nisselson, Evan (Box 25)
  - Nixon, Nicholas (2 folders) (Box 26)
  - Nobuyoshi, Fujiwara (Box 26)
  - Noel, Laura Allen (Box 26)
  - Noland, William (Box 26)
  - Norfleet, Barbara (Box 26)
  - Norris, Barry (Box 26)
  - O'Connor, Flannery (Box 26)
  - O'Connor, Rosalie (Box 26)
  - Oglesbee, Brian (Box 26)
  - Ogneov, Valentin (Box 26)
  - O'Hare, Patrick (Box 26)
  - Okun, Willy (Box 26)
  - Ollman, Arthur (Box 27)
  - Olmstead, Fredrick Law (2 folders) (Box 27)
  - Omenetto, Christine (Box 27)
  - O'Neil, Nancy Kavanagh (Box 27)
  - O'Neil, Robert Joseph (Box 27)
  - Orkin, Ruth (Box 27)
  - Orstadius, Martin (Box 27)
  - Osinski, Christine (Box 27)
  - Owens, Don (Box 27)
  - Owings, Gregory (Box 27)
  - Pachano, Peter (Box 27)
  - Packer, George (Box 27)
  - Padilla, Darcy (Box 27)
  - Padilla, Jennifer (Box 27)
  - Page, Susan (Box 27)
  - Papageorge, Tod (Box 28)
  - Pallotta, Lina (Box 28)
  - Parada, Esther (Box 28)
  - Parady, Judy (Box 28)
  - Paresky, Laura (Box 28)
  - Parker, Clare (Box 28)
  - Parker, Michael (Box 28)
  - Pastor, Nancy (Box 28)
  - Parr, Martin (Box 28)
  - Patrice, Susan (Box 28)
  - Patterson, Neil (Box 28)
  - Paul, Greg (Box 28)
  - Peattie, Peggy (Box 28)
  - Peck, Mary (Box 28)
  - Pellegrin, Paolo (Box 28)
  - Peress, Gilles (2 folders) (Box 28)
  - Perkis, Phil (Box 28)
  - Perkins, James (Box 28)
  - Perlman, Ilene (Box 28)
  - Peters, Ed (Box 28)
  - Peterson, Cheers Mark (Box 28)
  - Petrenko, Anatoly (Box 28)
  - Petroff, Paul (Box 28)
  - Pfhal, John (Box 28)
  - Pfontenhauer, Rachel (Box 28)
  - Phillips, Jan (Box 28)
  - Pierce, Olive (Box 28)
  - Pillar, Heather (Box 28)
  - Pilaro, Chris (Box 28)
  - Pilson, John (Box 28)
  - Pinckley, Donna (Box 28)
  - Pinderhughes, John (Box 28)
  - Pinkel, Sheila (Box 28)
  - Pinney, Melissa Ann (Box 28)
  - Pitts, Ves (Box 28)
  - Plachy, Sylvia (Box 29)
  - PoKempner, Marc (Box 29)
  - Poli, Mariella (Box 29)
  - Poniatowska, Elena (Box 29)
  - Porter, Louise (Box 29)
  - Post, Susan (Box 29)
  - Post, Susie (Box 29)
  - Postal, Johnathan (Box 29)
  - Prager, Brenda (Box 29)
  - Prancia, Steven (Box 29)
  - Pratt, Charles (Box 29)
  - Price, Daniel (Box 29)
  - Pushinsky, Ted (Box 29)
  - Putnum, Jesse Ward (Box 29)
  - Putnam, Michael (Box 29)
  - Quackenbush, Michael (Box 29)
  - Raab, Michael (Box 29)
  - Rabung, Mark (Box 29)
  - Rachman, Barron (Box 29)
  - Radin, Robin (Box 29)
  - Rainier, Chris (Box 29)
  - Ramirez, Joseph (Box 29)
  - Ranard, John (Box 29)
  - Randlett, Mary (Box 29)
  - Randazzo, Joseph (Box 29)
  - Rankin, Tom (Box 29)
  - Ranney, Ed (Box 29)
  - Rapport, Leonard (Box 29)
  - Ratner, David (Box 29)
  - Ravanesi, Bill (Box 29)
  - Ravid, Joyce (Box 29)
  - Ray, Gypsy (Box 29)
  - Read, David (Box 29)
  - Read, Tory (Box 29)
  - Rechberger, Kristin (Box 29)
  - Records, Shawn (Box 29)
  - Reed, David (Box 30)
  - Reed, Eli (Box 30)
  - Reichert, Robert (Box 30)
  - Reiff, Patricia (Box 30)
  - Rein, Ilana (Box 30)
  - Reiten, Julie (Box 30)
  - Rembisz, Rick (Box 30)
  - Rhodes, Marvin (Box 30)
  - Rice, Tim (Box 30)
  - Richards, Eugene (Box 30)
  - Richardson, Doug (Box 30)
  - Richardson, Nan (Box 30)
  - Richman, Brad (Box 30)
  - Richter, Curt (Box 30)
  - Rieger, Sonja (Box 30)
  - Riley, Chris (Box 30)
  - Robbins, David (Box 30)
  - Roberts, Ines E. (Box 30)
  - Robinson, Abby (Box 30)
  - Robinson, David (Box 30)
  - Roemer, Jon (Box 30)
  - Rodriguez, Joe (Box 30)
  - Rodrigues, Sebastian and Fran Antmann (Box 30)
  - Roma, Tom (8 folders) (Box 30)
  - Rome, Stuart (Box 31)
  - Rose, Alan (2 folders) (Box 31)
  - Rosen, Diana (Box 31)
  - Rosenstein, Peter (Box 31)
  - Rosenthal, Mel (Box 31)
  - Ross, Judith (Box 31)
  - Ross, Richard (Box 31)
  - Rosser, Ed (Box 31)
  - Rost, Yuri (Box 31)
  - Rostagni, Jean-Christian (Box 31)
  - Roster, Tom (Box 31)
  - Roth, Marissa (Box 31)
  - Rothenberg, Daniel (Box 31)
  - Rothman, Richard (Box 31)
  - Rouda, Bill (Box 31)
  - Rupp, Sheron (Box 31)
  - Rubenstein, Meridel (Box 32)
  - Ruben, Steven (Box 32)
  - Rusten, Shelly (Box 32)
  - Ryerson, Marjorie (Box 32)
  - Rynne, M.K. (Box 32)
  - Saah, Jim (Box 32)
  - Sacha, Bob (Box 32)
  - Sager (Box 32)
  - Saitta, Giuseppe (Box 32)
  - Salguereo, Carolina (Box 32)
  - Salinger, Adrienne (Box 32)
  - Salter, Jeffery Allan (Box 32)
  - Salvador, Cristina (Box 32)
  - Salvo, Dana (Box 32)
  - Salzmann, Lawrence (Box 32)
  - Sanders, Kim (Box 32)
  - Sandoval, George (Box 32)
  - Sandoval, Judith H. (Box 32)
  - Sartor, Margaret (2 folders) (Box 32)
  - Saville, Lynn (Box 32)
  - Savulich, Andrew (Box 32)
  - Scales, Jeffery Henson (Box 32)
  - Scans (Box 32)
  - Schaefer, Linda (Box 32)
  - Schatz, Howard (Box 32)
  - Scheer, Bill (Box 32)
  - Schendler, Virginia (Box 32)
  - Schles, Ken (Box 32)
  - Schmelling, Michael (Box 32)
  - Schmidt, Bastienne (Box 33)
  - Schmidt, Joachim (Box 33)
  - Schreibman, Jane (Box 33)
  - Schultz, Barbara (Box 33)
  - Schwartz, Janet (Box 33)
  - Schwartz, Jason (Box 33)
  - Schwartz, Robin (Box 33)
  - Schwartz, Staci (Box 33)
  - Schwartzreich, Paul (Box 33)
  - Scorsese, Martin (Box 33)
  - Scott, Allison (Box 33)
  - Scott, Anderson (Box 33)
  - Scruton, Fred (Box 33)
  - Seding, Volker (Box 33)
  - Seeing the Elephant (Shawn Aubitz) (Box 33)
  - Segal, Gregg (Box 33)
  - Seif, Bob (Box 33)
  - Sekaer, Peter (Box 34)
  - Serotta, Edward (Box 34)
  - Sgroi, Fabio (Box 34)
  - Shafren, Nigel (Box 34)
  - Shamblin, Barbara (Box 34)
  - Shambroom, Paul (Box 34)
  - Sheikh, Fazal (Box 34)
  - Shemper, Adam (Box 34)
  - Short, William and Willia Seidenberg (Box 34)
  - Shames, Steven (Box 34)
  - Shamis, Bob (Box 34)
  - Shapiro, Toni (Box 34)
  - Sharlin, Johnathan (Box 34)
  - Sharp, Trish (Box 34)
  - Sherbell, Shepard (Box 34)
  - Shirer, Stan (Box 34)
  - Sherman, Ken (Box 34)
  - Shifrin, Jean (Box 34)
  - Shimon, John and Julie Lindermann (Box 34)
  - Shook, Melissa (Box 34)
  - Shore, Stephen (Box 34)
  - Silberman, Robert (Box 34)
  - Silberman, Zia (Box 34)
  - Silbert, Layle (Box 34)
  - Sills, Vaughn (2 folders) (Box 34)
  - Simone, Chip (Box 34)
  - Sindler, Mark (Box 34)
  - Singh, Dayanita (Box 34)
  - Singh, Raghubir (Box 34)
  - Sira, Victor (Box 35)
  - Siskind, Lawrence (Box 35)
  - Sixth Street Photog Workshop (Maggie Perkins) (Box 35)
  - Sklar, Evan (Box 35)
  - Slavin, Neil (Box 35)
  - Sligh, Clarissa (Box 35)
  - Slesnick, Les (Box 35)
  - Sloan, John (Box 35)
  - Smith, Brad A. (Box 35)
  - Smith, D. K. (Box 35)
  - Smith, Lindy (Box 35)
  - Smith, Maggie (Box 35)
  - Smith, Steve (Box 35)
  - Smith, W. Eugene (2 folders) (Box 35)
  - Smogor, Linda (Box 35)
  - Snider, David (Box 35)
  - Solomon, Rosalind (Box 35)
  - Spano, Michael (Box 35)
  - Spear, David (Box 35)
  - Spears, Ross (Box 35)
  - Spiegel, Marjorie (Box 35)
  - Spragg, Stacia (Box 35)
  - Springsteen, Pamela (Box 35)
  - Spuntoff, Richard (Box 35)
  - Staller, Jan (Box 35)
  - Stamets, John (Box 35)
  - Stanton, C. E. (Box 35)
  - Stava, Susan (Box 35)
  - Stearn, Peter (Box 35)
  - Steber, Maggie (Box 35)
  - Steensma, Jennifer (Box 35)
  - Stein, Harvey (Box 35)
  - Steinmetz, Mark (Box 35)
  - Stern, Andrea (Box 35)
  - Sternfeld, Joel (2 folders) (Box 35)
  - Stewart, Sharon (Box 36)
  - Stilley, Ricky (Box 36)
  - Stock, David (Box 36)
  - Stone, Jim (Box 36)
  - Stone, Les (Box 36)
  - Stovall, Julie (Box 36)
  - Stratton, Margaret (Box 36)
  - Straw, Gerald (Box 36)
  - Street, Richard (Box 36)
  - Strong, Bruce (Box 36)
  - Stummer, Helen M. (Box 36)
  - Sturdevant, Sandra (Box 36)
  - Stylianon, Krystallena (Box 36)
  - Suchy, Miso (Box 36)
  - Sugerman, Debra (Box 36)
  - Sultan, Larry (Box 36)
  - Sundra, Michael (Box 36)
  - de Swaan, Sylvia (Box 36)
  - Swarts, Matt (Box 36)
  - Sweeney, Marla (Box 36)
  - Swinson, Lee (Box 36)
  - Swift, Thor (Box 36)
  - Szabo, Joseph (Box 36)
  - Szarkowski, John (2 folders) (Box 36)
  - Tarver, Ron (Box 36)
  - Tehrani, Alex (Box 36)
  - Tellgren, Anna (Box 36)
  - Temple, Charlotte (Box 36)
  - Tenneson, Joyce (Box 36)
  - Thall, Bob (Box 36)
  - Thibaut, Emiliano (Box 36)
  - Thode, Scott (Box 36)
  - Thomas, Chip (Box 36)
  - Thomas, Katrina (Box 36)
  - Thompson, Jerry (Box 37)
  - Thurber, Shellburne (Box 37)
  - Tice, George (2 folders) (Box 37)
  - Tirana, Amina (Box 37)
  - Tobin, Mark (Box 37)
  - Toensing, Amy (Box 37)
  - Tolan, William (Box 37)
  - Tonningsen, Peter (Box 37)
  - Toplikar, Susan (Box 37)
  - Torres, Aurelio (Box 37)
  - Touchet, Leo (Box 37)
  - Towell, Larry (3 folders) (Box 37)
  - Tourlentes, Stephen (Box 37)
  - Traikos, Lori (Box 38)
  - Traister, Michael (Box 38)
  - Traube, Alex (Box 38)
  - Tress, Arthur (Box 38)
  - Troeller, Linda (Box 38)
  - Tucker, Toba (Box 38)
  - Tulis, Thomas (Box 38)
  - Turczan, Katherine (Box 38)
  - Turk, Elizabeth (Box 38)
  - Turner, Michael (Box 38)
  - Turok, Antonio (Box 38)
  - Tynan, Jim (Box 38)
  - Urrea, Lewis (Box 38)
  - Uhlenbeck, Erica (Box 38)
  - Vachon, John (Box 38)
  - Vassiliov, Andreas (Box 38)
  - Vaughn, Caroline (Box 38)
  - Vernant, Pierre (Box 38)
  - Venezia, Anthony (Box 38)
  - Vera, Jorge (Box 38)
  - Verburg, JoAnn (Box 38)
  - Verene, Chris (Box 38)
  - Vergara, Camilo Jose (Box 38)
  - Vigtel, Gudman (Box 38)
  - Vitali, Massimo (Box 38)
  - Vizzini, Nancianne (Box 38)
  - Vizzini, Robert (Box 38)
  - Wade, Harry (Box 38)
  - Wagner, Catherine (Box 38)
  - Waldman, Max (Box 38)
  - Walker, Shawn (Box 39)
  - Wallace, Scott (Box 39)
  - Wallis, Dawna (2 folders) (Box 39)
  - Walsh, James (Box 39)
  - Walsh, Wendy (Box 39)
  - Walters, Joanne (Box 39)
  - Wang, Harvey (Box 39)
  - Ward, Frank (Box 39)
  - Warner, William (Box 39)
  - Waters, Tom (Box 39)
  - Watters, Diana (Box 39)
  - Webb, Alex (Box 39)
  - Weems, Carrie Mae (Box 39)
  - Wegman, W. (Box 39)
  - Weider, Alan (Box 39)
  - Weider, Mary (Box 39)
  - Weil, Brian (Box 39)
  - Weisbrot, Michael (Box 39)
  - Weiss, Hans (Box 39)
  - Weitz, Jessica (Box 39)
  - Wells, David (Box 39)
  - Welty, Eudora (Box 39)
  - Wemple, C.T. (Box 39)
  - West, Bruce and Sharon (Box 39)
  - West, Judy (Box 39)
  - West, William K. (Box 39)
  - Wharton, David (Box 39)
  - Whitehouse, Deborah (Box 39)
  - Wichs, Steve (Box 39)
  - Widmer, Christian (Box 39)
  - Willard, Tom (Box 39)
  - Williams, Graeme (Box 39)
  - Williams, Jeannette (Box 39)
  - Williams, Sye (Box 39)
  - Williamson, Michael (Box 39)
  - Willis, Deborah (Box 39)
  - Willis, John (Box 39)
  - Wilner, Augusta (Box 39)
  - Wilson, Harry (Box 39)
  - Wilson, Lee (Box 39)
  - Winogrand, Garry (Box 39)
  - Winogrand, Garry (Box 40)
  - Winokur, Michael (Box 40)
  - Wise, Marc (Box 40)
  - Withers, Ernest C. (Box 40)
  - Wohlheter, Walter P. (Box 40)
  - Wolf, Linda (Box 40)
  - Wolin, Jeffrey (Box 40)
  - Wolke, Joy (Box 40)
  - Wolvovitz, Ethel (Box 40)
  - Wood, Jasper (Box 40)
  - Wood, Tom (Box 40)
  - Woodman, Donald (Box 40)
  - Winningham, Geoff (Box 40)
  - Worswick, Clark (Box 40)
  - Wrbican, Sue (Box 40)
  - Wright, Corina (Box 40)
  - Wright, Holly (Box 40)
  - Wright, Willie Anne (Box 41)
  - Wynn, Jessica (Box 41)
  - Wynroth, Via (Box 41)
  - Yalom, Ben and Reid (Box 41)
  - Young, Barbara (Box 41)
  - Young, D.C. (Box 41)
  - Younker, Richard (Box 41)
  - Zeibell, Robert (Box 41)
  - Zeiger, David (Box 41)
  - Zelman, Bil (Box 41)
  - Zimbel, George (Box 41)